<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vanessa&#39;s &amp; Jaime&#39;s Wedding on V&amp;J</title>
    <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vanessa&#39;s &amp; Jaime&#39;s Wedding on V&amp;J</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/contact/</guid>
      <description> Please let us know as soon as possible if you can make it to the wedding and how many people will be joining you. We are looking forward to seeing you there! 😊
Also feel free to share any dietary restrictions, allergies, feelings or just tell us about your day. Your NameEmail AddressAn email address is required.Message</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/faq/</guid>
      <description>What to wear? 👗 Dresscode for the Cityhall is formal. We&amp;rsquo;d recommend dresses for women and suits for men.
Polterabend is going to be informal. We recommend to bring a jacket, as it might get a bit chilly in the evening.
Where to fly to? 🛫 Leipzig Airport (LEJ) is the closest airport. From there you can get to Wintzingerode/Worbis by car.
It&amp;rsquo;s also possible to take a plane to Frankfurt (FRA) and then catch a train to Göttingen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locations</title>
      <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/locations/</guid>
      <description>City Hall wedding Rathaus Rentamt
Rossmarkt 1
37339 Leinefelde-Worbis (Worbis)
Google Maps
How to get to the City Hall? If you stay in Worbis: You can probably walk there. Everything is close to each other.
It will probably take 10-15 minutes.
If you stay in Wintzingerode you can get there by car (5 minutes) or ask us&amp;hellip;actually ask Vanessa because Jaime is probably as lost as you are xD
There are probably more people coming so we could organize a carsharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/schedule/</guid>
      <description>City Hall Wedding Date: 25.08.2023
Meeting at the city hall: 1.45pm. We are in Germany, so please be punctual ;) Ceremony: Start at 2pm.
End approx. at 2.30pm
Time for drinks, taking pictures etc. until 3pm/3.30pm
Go to your location and prepare for the Polterabend:
Take a nap Go to the toilet Get dressed &amp;hellip; Polterabend Start: Around 6pm
End: Open end Food and drinks are going to be provided at all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to stay?</title>
      <link>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vschwerdt.github.io/web_weeding/info/sleep/</guid>
      <description>Suggested places to pass out 😴 Hotel 3 Rosen in Worbis (Closest to Cityhall): Link EICstay in Worbis: Link Burg Bodenstein: Link Gaststätte zur Linde in Wintzingerode (Closest to Polterabend): Link Leinotel in Leinefelde: Link Victor&amp;rsquo;s in Teistungen: Link Ask us if you need more information!
Note: if you know how to Google you might be able to find a better deal 💻</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
